<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BMW models</string>
    <array name="models">
        <item>1 Series</item>
        <item>2 Series</item>
        <item>3 Series</item>
        <item>4 Series</item>
        <item>5 Series</item>
        <item>6 Series</item>
        <item>7 Series</item>
        <item>8 Series</item>
        <item>X1 Series</item>
        <item>X2 Series</item>
        <item>X3 Series</item>
        <item>X4 Series</item>
        <item>X5 Series</item>
        <item>X6 Series</item>
        <item>X7 Series</item>
        <item>Z4 Series</item>
        <item>i3 Series</item>
        <item>i8 Series</item>
    </array>
    <array name="details">
        <item>The BMW 1 Series showcases a cleverly crafted sporty spirit and modern design. Explore attractive options for interior and exterior, dynamically optimized powertrain and chassis components, as well as innovative technologies and maintain to assist drivers.</item>
        <item>The BMW 2 Series Coupé is the essence of automotive individuality and creates its own class. The revolutionary sports design radiates motion even while standing. Its radical dynamics with a distinctly take-off rear-wheel drive and high level of comfort in an exclusive interior complete the uncompromising driving experience. This is obvious from the first moment: when you sit behind the wheel, there is only one way - forward.</item>
        <item>Having just hit the road, the all-new BMW 3 Series Sedan is already leaving everything behind, including conventions and expectations. Once again this icon shows how it manages to redefine itself. After all, with pioneering design language, it’s about the dawn of a new era. Even more powerful and efficient engines run the ultimate sports sedan. And a new force - simply say "Hey BMW" and the all-new BMW 3 Series recognizes your voice and listens to your every word.</item>
        <item>An athlete created to impress on the road. The result is impressive. More dynamics, agility and comfort. Uncompromisingly ready for action, offering design, impression and handling where everything is carefully optimized. In short: a beautiful sport coupé that gives pleasure in driving with new meaning and satisfying the most demanding users.</item>
        <item>His mission is to set new standards. The BMW 5 Series is the epitome of a modern business sedan. Thanks to its dynamic yet elegant appearance, it convincingly meets the expectations set today for vehicles of this class: sporty aesthetics and driving pleasure with state-of-the-art technology.</item>
        <item>The BMW 6 Series impresses with its unique aesthetics as well as its generous lavish and luxurious interior. Its superb driving characteristics guarantee sporty dynamics - and maximum ride comfort on long journeys. This vehicle is an expressive statement - of modern design and joy.</item>
        <item>Manage all performance, enjoy every moment. The BMW 7 Series Sedan features confident appearance, exceptional performance and maximum comfort. As the BMW 750Li is powered by the new BMW TwinPower Turbo eight-cylinder gasoline engine and the xDrive option as standard, it has simply been created to take the lead. The emotional language of elegant design coupled with a special atmosphere of well-being in the interior, thanks to the superior quality of detail, individual styling capabilities and technical innovations, make it the epitome of BMW luxury class. Smoothness meets exclusivity. Luxury meets performance.</item>
        <item>Strength. Control. Comfort. With its unique design, exceptional agility and impressive motors, the BMW 8 Series Coupé raises both the rev counter and the adrenaline level. Combined with exclusive racing features, the luxury sports car is the perfect blend of top quality and maximum performance.</item>
        <item>An important milestone: the new BMW X1 has come to set standards. His desire for action is shown primarily in athletic design. At first glance, its an X model entirely: its exterior features short overhangs and long wheelbase typical of a Sports Activity Vehicle (SAV). This makes his ambitions clear with convincing dynamics and agility. Thanks to its high versatility and flexibility combined with innovative technologies, it provides maximum comfort on every meter of driving.</item>
        <item>Absolutely unique. Very exceptional. The new BMW X2 clearly announces its sporting ambitions at a glance. With its bold sporting spirit, it delivers dynamic and agile performance that is unrivaled in this class. Paired with a high quality interior and many innovative technologies, he is the extroverted protagonist of the new era. Are you ready?</item>
        <item>The BMW X3 is a statement of unlimited possibilities and an expression of complete impression and freedom. From the first glance, he is fascinated by his sporty appearance and fascinated by the exciting driving experience. Thanks in part to its autonomous driving and intelligent all-wheel drive system, the BMW xDrive offers superior comfort both on and off the road. So he redefines benchmarks in his class and makes one thing clear: there is a big difference in how you get to your destinations.</item>
        <item>No matter what challenges come your way, the BMW X4 is more than ready to face them. His progressive design and coupe-like contours immediately reveal his need for action. And thanks to first-class driving dynamics, innovative lightweight construction with a low center of gravity and even higher levels of performance - there is only one thing standing between you and your destinations: sheer driving pleasure.</item>
        <item>The leader has arrived and is setting new rules: the all-new BMW X5. Its appearance is clear to all - upright, strong and elegant. A powerful one-piece double mask indicates what will happen when you need to take a deep breath. And the glossy X headlamp design leaves no doubt as to who will take the lead. Equipped with new technologies for greater safety and maximum driving dynamics on every surface, the new BMW X5 knows where it is going. And how to get there first.</item>
        <item>Uncompromisingly non-conformist - the new BMW X6 represents provocative confidence. On top of that, it is visible in the extremely sporty body of the vehicle, along with a new, distinctive design language, displaying it through superior exclusivity and visionary technologies, such as the impressive BMW - Iconic Glow grille. All of this points to one thing in the first place: absolute dominance, demonstrated by the new BMW X6 on almost every route thanks to its powerful engine, precision suspension and features like the xOffroad package. Experience a new unprecedented way to exceed expectations with the new BMW X6.</item>
        <item>Luxury Class Statement: The new BMW X7 is an elegant fusion of appearance and personality. Despite its magnificent appearance, it gives the impression of lightness and agility thanks to its purist design and athletic styling. At the same time, the spacious interior offers a pioneering collaboration of exclusivity, functionality and freedom - unmatched comfort up to the third row of seats. Charm is its essence. Elegance character.</item>
        <item>Once the roof is complete, there is no more restriction on driving pleasure in the new BMW Z4. A roadster that could not be better: open, sporty and uncompromising. With its powerful driving dynamics and progressive design, it has only one goal: freedom between the road and the open sky.</item>
        <item>Come in and experience the future at your fingertips. The BMW i3 is full of innovative technologies that can be used to reliably master everyday life. It connects you to the outside world, updates you on what is going on, organizes everything for you and guides you as far as you want to go. He is always ready for the road and exploring new routes. With style and design that sets trends for driving pleasure in electricity.</item>
        <item>The future takes shape - in the shape of the first ever BMW i8 Coupé. Full of flight, fascinating and ready for newly defined mobility. For unconditional driving pleasure, no matter how much the road. From the first look at the iconic design, adrenaline levels have been rising. The tachometer is growing just as fast: the innovative hybrid plug-in engine generates 374 hp and 570 Nm. In addition, it enables the new BMW i8 Coupé to accelerate from 0 to 100 km / h in just 4.4 seconds. The fastest way to a new era.</item>
    </array>
</resources>
